this is my first file
Name: Elad Galmidi
Date: 25-02-2026

Lab 2 - Git Basic Commands
===========================

1. Answer: git branch branch-name
2. Answer: git switch
3. Answer: git fetch downloads changes from the remote repository but does not merge them.
           git pull downloads changes and automatically merges them into the current branch.
4. Answer: git checkout branch-b
           Then run:
           git merge branch-a
5. Answer: git push origin branch-name
